# NATHANAEL ERNEST DENYS

San Mateo, CA, 94403 · (650) 922 - 0740 · natedenys@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/nathan-denys

## **SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS**

I am a performance driven individual seeking a position in Front End Web Development. I have six years of experience overseeing and enhancing the value of small businesses. Throughout my experience, I maintain precise records and transactions of all business functions that promote and excel the operations within the business. Transcending vendor and customer relations are the top priority in market based functions and ensuring the business is operating above satisfactory procedures.

## **EDUCATION**

University of Irvine, Irvine CA

May 2015

## **Bachelor of Science in Business Economics**

Codify Academy, San Francisco, CA

May 2017

## **Front-End Web Development**

• Relevant Coursework: API's, Python, Vue, Bootstrap, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, jQuery, & React

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Oh Baby Sushi

December 2017 - Current

## **Front of House Leader**

- Managing the day-to-day front of house operations including: opening the restaurant, assisting guests with all aspects of their orders, money management, cleaning, and closing the restaurant
- Adapting to new Point of Sale Clover programs and onboarding new hires to the system
- Providing support to staff to encourage teamwork as a leader and example in creating a harmonious environment
- Ensuring all service requests, communication, appearance, and repairs are completed on a timely basis
- Maintaining a safe work environment for all employees and guests following CDC guidelines & restrictions
- Uninterrupted first-hand guest service in-out of the door
- Presenting food and beverage knowledge; making recommendations complementing individuals taste
- Operating at high efficiency level responding with clear communication throughout the entire team

Zanette Aviation Insurance, San Carlos CA

September 2015 - December 2017

## Administrative Assistant

- Managed small business website including debugging
- Shortened development process for renewals and invoices through Pleasure & Business
- Increased customer account retention; consistent growth of 5+ accounts per month
- Conducted policy renewal for current accounts and forecasting business growth

Trader Joe's, San Mateo, CA

April 2015 - July 2017

## **Section Leader**

- Supervised the alcohol section: product knowledge, section orders, forecasting product sales
- Developed an unprecedented teamwork ethic, quick adaptability, and high multitasking skills

- Sustained attention to detail through product rotation, opening/closing several sections, breaking down large pallets, checking off manifests, staging products, and building end caps
- Contributed clear communication with managers, crew members, and guests

# ADDITIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

- Microsoft Word and Excel
- Professionalism, Integrity, Drive, Creativity
- Enthusiastic Leader
- High Attention to Detail
- Emotional Intelligence
- Enhancing Value
- Knowledgeable on Current Laws